Chanservain Ibaka



Contacts

Address:

Hyderabad. India

Phone:

+91 9618086913

Email:

Chanservain.ibaka@gmail.com

Website:

http://www.chanservainibaka.com/

Languages

French: Native language

Lingala: Native Language

English: Good

Hobbies

- Football
- Music
- Travelling
- Gastronomy

Summary

Senior linguistic translator specializing in Lingala. Experienced with large projects. Well-versed in numerous languages including English, Lingala and French, using software like Trados Studio SDL, Wordfast etc.

Web developer with more than 4 years of experience. Including HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript ES6, Bootstrap 5, Agile methodology, etc. I am also passionate about Backend such as Python (Django 2.2 or 3+), Node Js, SQL, etc.

Work Experience

Translator – 06/2019 to date <u>Babelos Ltd</u>, Nigeria

- Translate documents from/to Lingala, English.
- Proofreading.

Internship trainer – 12/2016 to 07/2017 Knowledge Sharing Campaign, Hyderabad – India

- In charge of selecting internship candidates.
- Full Stack Developer Group Team Leader.
- Trainee training in Python Diango.

IT Director – 10/2015 to 11/2016 <u>African Student Association (ASA-TS)</u>, Hyderabad – India

- Creation and the maintenance of the association website.
- Informing all register members through social media pages.

Education

Bachelor of Science

Osmania University, India

Graduation: 2020

Major: Computer programing

Skills

- Project management
- Translation
- UI/UX Developer
- Microsoft Word & Excel
- Figma

- Creative design
- Joomla, WordPress
- Innovative
- SDL Trados Studio
- Trello